zobello.com 2017-06-06

# Zobello Privacy Policy

Zobello respects the privacy of all visitors to its website and is highly committed to maintaining the privacy of all online visitors to its website [www.zobello.com](https://www.zobello.com/).

We will use your data to make sure that your orders will be handled as fast and easy as possible or that certain parts of sites are more tailored to your interests. However, we will not share your Personally Identifiable ‘Information’ with others without your prior consent. This document describes how we deal with your online privacy and online security.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use it and whether we will disclose it to anyone.

The outline of this document:

1\. What information we collect   
2\. We don’t share your information  
3\. Your information is safe at Zobello (Online Security)   
4\. Cookies   
5\. Controlling your information with us   
6\. Contact us at Zobello

**1\. What information we collect**

We may collect information when you register for promotional emails, set up a shopping account, purchase goods, contact customer service, or engage in other interactive features with our sites (e.g., customer feedback, opinion surveys, service feedback etc.). This information may also include your name, address, email id and phone number. Please also review our online **Terms & Conditions**, which are linked at the bottom of our websites and govern many of the user-generated content and related features, as explained therein.

  * If you place an order on zobello.com , we collect your name, e-mail address, mobile number, billing and shipping information in order to complete and deliver your order.

  * To make your shopping experience as nice as possible we, with your permission, collect personal information about your orders and the use of our services. With this information we can personalize the website and recommend products you might be interested in.

  * We collect your information in an aggregated form to compile statistical and demographical profiles for our marketing and rebranding activites.

If you make an account at Zobello we will collect your information on a secure server. You are asked to fill in your name, e-mail address, billing and shipping information so that you don’t have to fill in this again for any following purchases.

  * The information we collect about both the use of our site(s) and the feedback help us to develop and improve the website(s).

With your permission we will inform you on new features, specials and other promotional activities of Zobello. If you do not want this, you can change this in your account settings or send us an e-mail at [unsubscribe@zobello.com](mailto:unsubscribe@zobello.com).

Should you apply for a job at Zobello, whether through the website, by e-mail or mail, we require you to supply us with your personal information, resume and application letter.

**2\. We don’t share your information:**

We will not share (or sell) the information you provide us with third parties unless we first obtain your consent. We will also give you the opportunity of opting out of other uses that we might make of any of the information you provide to us.

Please note that the use of any feature made available to you on our websites such as Facebook Connect, may result in information being collected or shared about you by us or by others. We cannot control how your information is collected, stored, used or shared by third-party sites or to whom it is disclosed. Please be sure to review the privacy policies and settings on your social networking sites to make sure you understand and agree with the information they are sharing.

If you do not want Zobello to share information about you with a social media site or application, you should not access the social media site or the social media applications. For example, you should not click on Facebook icon on a product detail page.

**3\. Your information is safe at** **Zobello**

**(Online Security)**

We appreciate the trust you place in us. Zobello is committed to protecting your personal information. We’ve implemented reasonable security measures, including Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology and other tools to protect all your information we might collect on our websites. We use a variety of measures to ensure that your personal information is protected from: unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification or alteration, unlawful destruction or accidental loss. However, the Internet is an open system and Zobello cannot guarantee that the personal information you submit will not be intercepted by others.

All our employees who have access to or are involved in the processing of personal information respect the confidentiality of personal information.

Our website may include links to external websites operated by other organizations. They may collect personal information from visitors to their site. Zobello cannot guarantee the content or privacy practices of any external websites and does not accept responsibility for those websites.

We reserve the right to disclose any information to the extent we reasonably believe that disclosure is required by law, to enforce our website policies, or to protect your or others" rights, property or safety.

**4\. Cookies**

We may use ‘cookies’ on our website that act as an identification card for your computer. When you visit zobello.com website, unique cookies are placed to distinguish your browser from all other browsers that visit our sites. By recognizing your browser, we can serve you better.

You have a choice to accept or reject cookies by modifying your browser preferences. You have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set or to reject all cookies. **Please note that if you choose to reject all cookies, certain parts of this site may not be available to you or may not function properly.**

**5\. Controlling your information with us**

By submitting your personal information, you give your consent to the use of said information as set out in this privacy policy. You have the following rights to change your information: a right to see the information we hold on you, a right to have any wrong or incomplete information corrected, or (in certain circumstances) to have your personal information deleted, a right to ask us to stop providing you information on our services.

**6\. Contact us at** **Zobello**

If you have any questions, feedback or want to know more about how your personal information is used, or if you want to access, correct or remove your personal information, please contact us at [customer-care@zobello.com](mailto:customer-care@zobello.com) .
